SARIT SOPITVETMONTREE

PRODUCT DESIGNER

Yokohama, Kanagawa 070-1262-9500 sarit.sopitvetmontree@gmail.com

PROFILE

Product Designer with diverse experience across industries like 3D printing, healthcare, and quantum computing, currently focused on Al agent and B2B solution. Experienced in designing products in the zero-to-one phase. Skilled in frontend development, enabling effective collaboration with developers and understanding engineering constraints. Fluent in Thai, English, and Japanese.

Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarit-sopitvetmontree/

SKILL LANGUAGE

UX design, User flow, Wireframing, Competitive research UI design, Design system, Responsive design, Brand alignment HTML, CSS, Typescript, React, MUI, Tailwind, VSCode, Git/Github JapaneseJLPT N2EnglishTOEIC 960 TOEFL 99ThaiNative

WORK EXPERIENCE

Product Designer

November 2024 - Present

Sales Marker, Tokyo - Al SaaS company

- Lead the experience and interface design for Orcha, an Al agent application
- Create and improve the design of Al products related to sales and marketing
- Work on the design system to ensure usability, branding, and consistency of the UI

Product Designer

Contract July 2024 - October 2024

SIND Inc., Tokyo - Healthcare software company

- Design Caretomo, an Al SaaS companion app for nurses and doctors in a large hospitals
- Create a design system from scratch for the brand identity and UI consistency

UX Engineer Aug 2023 – October 2024

QunaSys, Tokyo - Quantum computer software company

- Develop and improve web applications using Next.js with MUI and related technologies
- Design and adjust web application design in Figma based on data from user research

UX/UI Designer

Contract July 2023 - October 2023

Digitech Fabrication, Bangkok - 3D printing service company

- Creat a design system, sitemap, and high-fidelity design for the 3D printing service app
- Work together with developer to deliver the website with a contribution to coding

EDUCATION

The University of Tokyo 東京大学

April 2022 - March 2024

Master's Degree, Department of Aeronautics and Astronautics

Chulalongkorn University จุฬาลงกรณ์มหาวิทยาลัย

August 2017 - July 2021

Bachelor's Degree, Department of Mechanical Engineering (Second-class honors)

ACHIEVEMENT & CERTIFICATE

MEXT Scholarship Awarded the MEXT Scholarship by the Embassy of Japan in Thailand Olympiad in Informatics Selected to participate in the 12th Thailand Olympiad of Informatics